《诉讼双雄》前情提要
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我来这里是想请你回家的
I'm here because I want you to come home.
回到律所吗
Back to the firm?
没错  不仅如此
Yes, and not only that,
你可以让罗伯特·赞恩的
you can get the ten best associates
首席翻译官
█ 网易见外
十个最棒的新律师跟你一起来
from Robert Zane's stable to come with you.
我能从中得到什么好处
And what's in this for me?
我保证你将成为我们有史以来
I'll make sure that you are the youngest senior partner
首席校对官
人人译视界
·
人人
最年轻的资深合伙人
we've ever had.
今早我们就和罗伯特·赞恩律所合并了
As of this morning, we're merging with Robert Zane.
我当时来的时候你说我会
When I came over, you said my name
翻译     arcadiachi  Alex  苏葵   小溪1120
成为下一个冠名合伙人
would be the one to go up next.
我向你保证
You have my word.
你会是下一个冠名合伙人
Your name goes up next.
亚历克斯  你干什么呢
Alex, what are you doing?
我要看萨曼莎·惠勒的所有案件记录
I'm going through every one of Samantha Wheeler's files,
翻译     Giggles  斗斗  克里斯托啊托  木浅
因为大战要来了  我要做准备
'cause a fight's coming, and I'm gonna be ready.
卡特里娜  你确定亲自开掉曾经和你
Katrina, are you sure you're gonna be okay
校对     木浅
共事数年的人对你来说没问题吗
firing people you've worked with for years?
我要告诉你我和路易说的话
I'll tell you what I told Louis,
如果我要在这里演好自己的角色
that if I'm going to grow in my role here,
时间轴     张小满   caroline
这就是我必须学着去做的事之一
this is something I'm going to have to learn to do.
你公然藐视我给你的任务
I gave you an order, and you blatantly ignored me.
后期     斯人
我确实做了你原先要求的事
I did do what you originally asked:
就是客观的评价各位律师
to objectively evaluate the associates.
我不管  布莱恩必须留下
I don't care. Brian is staying.
总监     木浅
盖文·安德鲁不只是表面上那样
Gavin Andrews is a hell of a lot more than meets the eye.
有你之前的黑历史  我以为你会更小心
And a guy with your history would want to be more careful
┌
┐
└
┘
人人影视官方客户端
唯一下载渠道
app.YYeTs.com
┌
┐
└
┘
在与谁合作上更谨慎些
about who he gets into bed with.
那告诉我你指的是什么事
Tell me what you're talking about,
否则离开我的办公室
or get out of my goddamn office.
我承认  我开始看到她的能力了
I admit I'm starting to see what you see in her.
我别无他求
That's all I was hoping for.
现在  我可以告诉你为什么了
Now I can tell you why I was hoping it.
你还有什么没告诉我的
What haven't you told me?
下一个当冠名合伙人的是她
Her name goes up on the wall next.
我怎么会知道
I mean, how was I supposed to know
-她已婚了  -我说不准
- she was married? - I don't know,
或许她手上的结婚戒指能给你个提示
maybe her wedding ring could have tipped you off.
我当时23岁  你懂的
I was 23, you know?
我根本没注意到该死的戒指
I wasn't looking at no damn rings.
你年轻的时候还是很有胆量的
You really had some balls when you were younger.
现在也有  多谢夸奖
Still do, thank you very much.
说说你有什么事吧
Now, why don't you get to it?
说什么
Why don't I get to what?
哈维  能和你喝酒的朋友有的是
Harvey, you've got plenty of friends to have drinks with,
多数还比我长得好看
most of them prettier than me.
你心里有事
You've got something on your mind.
-说出来吧  -罗伯特  你还记得
- Let's hear it. - Robert, do you remember
你之前告诉我你答应萨曼莎
when you told me you promised Samantha
-她会成为下一个冠名合伙人  -记得
- her name would go up next? - I do.
我也向亚历克斯承诺过
I made Alex the same promise.
-为何现在告诉我  -因为我们是合伙人
- Why you telling me now? - Because we're partners.
我不想对我的合伙人有所隐瞒
I don't want to keep any secrets from my partner.
那在我看来只有一个办法
Then I guess there's only one thing to do.
-什么办法  -"踢皮球"
- What's that? - Kick the can down the road.
因为我们想要同时守住承诺
Because there's no way both of us are gonna be able
是不可能的  而且我们都清楚
to keep that promise, and for all we know,
在我们作出决定之前
one of them could get hit by a bus
他们也许会有人出车祸呢
before we have to make that call.
这么说来很庆幸我们俩的名字
Then I guess it's a good thing both our names
-已经挂在墙上了  -是啊
- are already up there. - Sure is.
-再来一杯  -好的  给我来双份的
- Another drink? - Yeah, make it a double.
你这是要去哪儿
And where are you going?
腾个肚子再继续喝
To make room for that double.
抱歉  能麻烦你回避一下我方便...
Excuse me, would you mind giving me a minute to...?
不好意思  我没听到你进来了
Oh, I'm so sorry, I-- I didn't hear you come in.
-我这就出去  -你没事吧
- Um, I'll just go. - Are you all right?
没事
Uh, yeah.
我刚刚接到一通电话
I, um--I just got a phone call.
没什么事
Um, it's not important.
-抱歉  -不用  你别走
- Excuse me. - No, you stay.
我去楼下
I'll use the one downstairs.
你想待多久都行
Take as long as you need.
不管怎样...
For what it's worth...
我希望你一切顺利
I hope everything's okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
你来我家干什么
What are you doing in my home?
因为我有办法拿回你那副雷诺阿画了
I'm here because I have a way to get your Renoir back,
但我需要从你这里拿点东西
but I'm gonna need something from you.
你想要什么
And what exactly is that?
把波尔多的别墅给你前妻
Give your ex the villa in Bordeaux,
并且保证她不用出一分钱维修费
and guarantee she never pays a nickel of upkeep.
我为什么要这么做
And why would I do that?
因为是你让我帮你把画拿回来的
Because you asked me to get that painting back
这是唯一的解决办法
and this is the only way that's gonna happen.
不  我是说你们律所要和我最大的
No, I mean why would I do that
竞争对手签约  我为什么还这么做
when your firm is about to sign my biggest competitor?
-你在说什么  -我刚刚得知
- What are you talking about? - I just learned
萨曼莎·惠勒准备签下德尔塔
Samantha Wheeler's about to sign Delta.
-该死  -对吧  我以为
- God damn it. - See, I thought
我说的很明白了  如果我和你签约
I made it clear that if I sign with you
我得相信你才行
it is because I trust you.
利用我来掩人耳目可并没让我觉得
Using me as a stalking horse doesn't make me feel like
-我可以相信你  -盖文  事情
- I can trust you. - Gavin, that's not
-不是这样的  -我告诉过你
- what's going on here. - I told you,
那副画对我个人很重要
that painting is personal to me.
我告诉你原因吧
I'm gonna tell you why.
我父亲并不富有
My father was not a wealthy man,
但他是个有教养的人
but he had an education.
如果说他最看重的
If there's one thing he appreciated
一样东西  那就是艺术作品
more than anything, it was art.
每逢周日  我们会去各种画廊
Every Sunday, we'd go to a different gallery.
我们会信步走着  他会对这里
We'd walk through-- he would tell me
所有他知道的作品讲解给我听
everything he knew about every painting there was.
你知道他最喜欢的艺术家是谁吗
You know who his favorite artist was?
雷诺阿
Renoir.
我买那副画花了八百万
I paid $8 million for that painting.
如今市值翻倍  但我绝不会拿去卖...
It's worth twice that now, but I would never sell it...
因为每次我看着它...
because every time I look at it...
我会想到我父亲
I think of him.
盖文  我告诉过你我会帮你拿到那副画
Gavin, I told you I'll get that painting back
我说到做到
and I will.
而且我再告诉你一件事
And I'll tell you something else--
萨曼莎·惠勒绝不会
There's no way Samantha Wheeler's signing
和德尔塔航空公司签约的
Delta goddamn Airlines.
咖啡
谢谢
Thanks.
亚历克斯  没想到在这儿见到你
Alex, what a pleasant surprise.
废话少说
Cut the bullshit.
我刚刚知道你对德尔塔航空公司下手了
I just found out you're going after Delta Airlines.
不是准备下手  这已经是板上钉钉的事
Not just going after, it's practically a done deal.
鉴于你刚发现我向盖文·安德鲁下手
That was fast, since you only talked to Delta
你就和德尔塔通了电话  动作可真迅速
after you found out I was pursuing Gavin Andrews.
这两件事没什么关系
One had nothing to do with the other.
我说了你别和我兜圈子
And I said cut the bullshit.
你这么做是因为或者你签下德尔塔
You did this because you knew you'd either sign Delta
我将处于不利位置
and I'd be out in the cold,
或者盖文·安德鲁指责我
or Gavin Andrews would accuse me
利用他掩人耳目
of using him as a stalking horse
也会置我于不利局面
and I'd be out in the cold.
如果这么肯定
If you're so sure of that,
那你为什么到这里来
then what are you doing standing here
毁掉我吃百吉饼早餐的兴致
ruining my morning bagel?
我来告诉你别再插手了
I'm here to tell you to back the hell off.
这是不可能的
Well, that's not gonna happen.
听我说
Listen to me.
我不知道你以前是怎么干活的
I don't know how you did things before,
但在这里  我们不互相背后捅刀子
but around here, we don't stab each other in the back.
那你找上我的老客户
Then what do you call going after my old client
为了让我难堪又算什么
for the sole purpose of making me look bad?
因为我可不会睁一只眼闭一只眼
Because I'm not gonna let that slide.
而且我警告过你
Not to mention I warned you
盖文·安德鲁不值得花这么大功夫
Gavin Andrews isn't worth the trouble.
你不想出丑
You don't want to look bad,
还是这个客户太棘手
or the client's too much trouble?
-哪一个  -都是
- Which one is it? - It's both,
如果连这也看不出来  那不是我的问题
and if you can't see that then it's not my problem.
我看到的是你挡在我和我客户之间
What I see is you standing between me and a client,
如果我是你  就赶紧撤
and if I were you, I'd get the hell out of the way.
那你最好赶快签下你的客户
Well, then you'd better sign your guy fast,
因为我离我的只有一码距离了
because I'm already on the one-yard line with mine
而且我马上要得分了
and I'm about to punch it in.
*看到钱  就愿意留下吃饭*
♪ See the money, wanna stay for your meal ♪
*给你太太再拿块馅饼*
♪ Get another piece of pie for your wife ♪
*所有人都想知道那感觉*
♪ Everybody wanna know how it feel ♪
*所有人都想见见那景象*
♪ Everybody wanna see what it's like ♪
*豆子馅饼我也愿吃  我不在乎*
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie, I don't mind ♪
*我和妹子忙着赚钱*
♪ Me and Missy is so busy, busy making money ♪
*好了*
♪ All right ♪
*退开点  我要跳舞*
♪ All step back, I'm 'bout to dance ♪
诉讼双雄
第八季 第三集
*美钞爵士摇摇摇*
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
早上好  罗伯特
Good morning, Robert.
等这该死的宿醉消失才算是早上好
It will be once this damn hangover wears off.
-昨晚出去嗨了吗  -不  就在这里
- Out late last night, yo? - Uh, no, I was here
忘了年龄  试图和哈维比拼喝酒
forgetting my age and matching Harvey drink for drink.
-有什么事吗  -罗伯特
- Now, what can I do for you? - Robert, you know,
如果你头疼  我可以做我奶奶的特效药
if you're hungover, I can whip up my nana's special remedy.
只需要一些糖  茶  热牛奶
I just need some sugar, tea, a little steamed milk,
当然还有我的两个护膜
and, of course, two of my cuticles.
谢了  我宁愿宿醉
Thanks, but I'd rather have the hangover.
是因为茶  对吧
It's about the tea, isn't it?
因为她来自古老的乡村
Because she's from the old country
-但我可以替换  -路易
- and I can substitute-- - Louis.
你到底过来干什么
What in God's name did you come in here for?
好吧  罗伯特
Okay. Robert.
还记得那天我觉得自己被排挤了
The other day when I was feeling left out,
然后你和哈维告诉我你们没有忘记我
you and Harvey let me know that you clocked me.
我意识到自己也有一阵子
Well, I realized that there's someone
没有关注过某人了
that I haven't been clocking.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
当我把卡特里娜从你那里挖过来时
When I brought Katrina over from you,
我答应过她  她会成为
I told her that she was gonna be
律所历史上最年轻的资深合伙人
the youngest senior partner in firm history,
我想实现那个承诺
and I want to fulfill that promise.
让我捋捋清楚
Now, let me get this straight:
你让我遵守你对她的承诺
you're holding me to a promise you made to her
好让你把她从我这里偷走
so that you could steal her from me.
罗伯特  你知道我不是这个意思
Robert, that's not the point and you know it.
卡特里娜是个很棒的律师  是时候了
Katrina is a great lawyer, and it's time.
也许  但是资深合伙人
Maybe it is time, but senior partner
不仅仅需要律师技巧  路易
isn't just "Lawyering," Louis.
更需要管理技巧  我不知道
It's about managing people, and I don't know
卡特里娜·班尼特与人相处技巧如何
how good Katrina Bennett is with people.
那你告诉我
Well, then you tell me.
她要怎样才能向你证明她的能力
What can she do to prove herself to you?
打扰了  斯佩克特先生
Excuse me, Mr. Specter?
-我记得你  -昨晚我们见过
- I know you, you're-- - From last night.
我...
I, uh...
想把这个还给你
wanted to return this.
你真是太好了  谢谢
You were very kind. Thank you.
没什么  我只希望一切都好
It's nothing. I was just hoping everything was okay.
事实上  我来这里是有事相求
Actually, that's the reason that I'm here.
-什么意思  -昨晚我很伤心
- What do you mean? - I was upset last night
是因为我接到了我母亲的电话
because I got a call from my mother.
她需要做手术  但我负担不起
She needs an operation, and I can't afford it.
你想要我做什么
What are you asking me?
我加了足够的班
I've worked enough overtime hours
来赚取手术的钱
to make having that operation possible,
但他们不给我加班费  因为我的职称是
but they won't pay me overtime because my title
设备经理[美国管理层不拿加班工资]
is Facilities Manager.
可我并不管理任何东西
I don't manage anything.
我希望也许
I was hoping maybe...
-我可以帮你把钱要回来  -是的
- I'd be able to get you your money. - Yes.
-听着  您是  -安娜
- Listen, Miss...? - Anna.
安娜·里德
Anna Reed.
安娜  你的雇主是我的房东
Anna, your employer is my landlord,
如果我介入事情可能会变得复杂
so if I get involved things could get very complicated.
但我只是想拿回属于我的工钱
But it's a simple matter of paying me for my work.
如果这是真的  他都不听你的话
If that were true, why would he listen to me
又怎么会听我说呢
when he didn't listen to you?
因为他们那样的大人物
Because people like me don't matter
不在乎我这样的小角色
to people like them.
我只是打扫厕所的人而已
I'm just the lady that cleans their toilet.
求你了  斯佩克特先生
Please, Mr. Specter.
向你开口并不容易
I'm not proud to ask you for this
但我母亲需要手术  一旦涉及到
but my mother needs this, and when it comes
照顾我们所爱的人
to taking care of people we love,
就顾不上那么多了
pride has no place.
好吧
Okay.
我不能保证任何事  但我会试试
I can't promise anything, but I'll try.
谢谢
Thank you.
我知道你很善良
I knew you were kind.
别告诉我你开始和清洁工约会了
Don't tell me you're dating the cleaning woman now.
-如果是呢  -那我恭喜你
- And what if I was? - I'd say congratulations.
不如你告诉我她来这儿的原因
But why don't you tell me why she was here.
昨晚我在厕所撞见她
I ran into her in the bathroom last night.
她当时在哭
She was crying.
大楼的人没有付给她应得的工资
The building isn't paying her what she's owed,
她让我去调查一下
and she asked me to look into it.
你是说她让你去和我们的房东干仗
You mean, she asked you to pick a fight with our landlord,
我得告诉你我们的房东
who I shouldn't have to tell you
可是个小气的混蛋
is a mean son of a bitch,
这不是个好主意
and this is a bad idea.
罗伯特  我不是白痴
Robert, I'm not an idiot,
我不会和大卫·福克斯作对的
and I'm not picking any fights with David Fox.
只是去和他谈几分钟
I'm gonna talk to the man for two minutes.
如果他不同意我的观点  那就算了
If he doesn't see it my way, that's it.
相信我
Trust me.
好吧  哈维
Okay, Harvey.
我相信你
I trust you.
原来你在这里  我到处找你
There you are. Been looking all over for you.
路易  如果这事可以等等
Louis, if there's any chance whatever it is can wait...
不行  我需要你监督布莱恩·阿特曼
It can't. I need you to supervise Brian Altman.
什么  路易  我手中有个案子
What? Louis, I am in the middle of a case,
一小时内就有个大会议
and there is a huge meeting in an hour.
那就让他帮你
Well, then have him help you with it.
我不需要帮助
I don't need any help,
现在我也没办法辅导别人
and I can't be mentoring someone right now.
不是辅导  而是管理
It's not mentoring; it's managing.
那就找别人管理他
Then have someone else manage him.
该死  卡特里娜
Damn it, Katrina,
这是你成为资深合伙人的机会
this is your chance to be senior partner.
-我的天  -没错
- Oh, my God. - That's right.
我刚刚和罗伯特·赞恩谈过了
I just talked to Robert Zane
关于履行我对你的承诺
about making good on my promise to you.
我甚至都不该告诉你  这是保密的
And I shouldn't even be telling you this-- no one can know.
他是支持的  只要你能够展现
He's on board as long as you can show
作为一个管理者应有的素养
that you are a manager.
好的  帮我个忙好吗
Okay, uh... Look, then just do me a favor.
让布莱恩自己先熟悉毕格罗纺织
Please just tell Brian to familiarize himself with Bigelow Textiles
然后四十五分钟后来会议室见我
and meet me in the conference room in 45 minutes.
有什么问题吗  卡特里娜
Katrina, is something going on?
为什么非得有什么问题呢
Why would something be going on?
我说不好  但就我刚才告诉你
I don't know, 'cause I just told you
你的梦想要成真的时候
that your dreams are coming true
你好像吃了坏了的牡蛎一样在犯恶心
and it looks like you ate a bad clam.
我很抱歉  路易
I'm sorry, Louis.
我的确很高兴  只是日程太紧
This is amazing news. I'm just crunched for time.
拜托了  告诉布莱恩让他准时来
So, please, just tell Brian to be there
我会从现在开始帮他处理
and I will handle him from here on out.
我会告诉他的
Okay, I'll let him know.
大卫·福克斯
David Fox.
我是哈维·斯佩克特
I'm Harvey Specter.
你是那个什么斯佩克特-利特来的
Of, uh, Something, Something, Specter Litt?
别告诉我我们公司换个名字
Don't tell me us changing our name
-也算个事儿  -并没有
- is gonna be an issue again. - No, it's not.
唐娜·鲍尔森做事没得挑
Donna Paulsen saw to that in your new lease.
唐娜对于达成她的目标的确有一套办法
Well, Donna has a way of getting what she wants.
说到达成目标
Speaking of what people want,
告诉我为什么你来这儿吧
why don't you tell me why you're here.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
我们楼层有一个清洁女工
There's a cleaning woman on our floor
付不起她母亲的医疗费
who can't afford to pay her mother's medical bills.
后来发现她严格来说是个设备经理
Turns out technically she's a facilities manager,
这根本就是她永远无法企及的高度
which means she's not eligible to make overtime.
一个有经理头衔的清洁工
A maid with a manager's title.
听上去她还挺受鼓舞
I mean, sounds to me like she's being empowered.
我俩都心知肚明  这个头衔不过是
You and I both know that title is just a way
为了逃避付她应得的工资
to get around paying what she's earned.
-我不懂你在说什么  -放屁
- I don't know any such thing. - Oh, bullshit.
-她是你的员工  -你说错了
- She's your employee. - Wrong.
我可是把公司所有的清洁业务外包
I contract all my cleaning services out
给别的企业  那些不是我名下的
to another company, a company I don't run.
你要告诉我那家公司难道不只是
You're gonna tell me that company is anything more
一张文书和一个邮箱地址而已吗
than a piece of paper and a PO Box?
你怎么不自己去实地考察一下
Why don't you pay them a visit and find out?
你听着  大卫  我只要求
Listen, David, all I'm asking
你做一件好事
is do the right thing.
-付给她应得的酬劳  -我说
- Pay her for her work. - You know,
你怎么不自掏腰包
why don't you reach into your own pocket?
因为那正是你在要我做的事
'Cause that's what you're asking me to do.
我要是付她钱  就得给所有清洁工发钱
And I do this for her, I gotta do it for everyone.
如果你不付她工资
And if you don't do it for her,
那你就得付所有清洁工的工资
you will have to do it for everyone.
我建议你看牢自己的嘴
You'd better watch what you say to me,
你可别忘了
'cause in case you forgot,
你还是在为我打工呢
you're still living under my roof.
你要是不想让步
And if you don't back off,
我会让你的公司地动山摇
I'll take that roof and everything else you have,
你可是刚违反了六条法律
because you just violated half-a-dozen laws
因为威胁你的租户
by threatening a tenant.
想跟我开战
You want to take me on,
你尽管来  我坐的这个位子
you go for it, 'cause I didn't get where I am
可不是随便让人威胁来的
by letting people like you push me around.
上回  唐娜都把你整的屁滚尿流
Last time, Donna kicked your ass.
而我不是唐娜
Well, I'm not Donna,
所以你还是乖乖地付我的委托人工钱吧
so you pay my client what you owe her.
-亚历克斯  -我们得谈谈萨曼莎·惠勒
- Alex. - We need to talk about Samantha Wheeler.
-这是什么意思  -意思是她正在
- What does that mean? - It means she's making a play
抢德尔塔航空  我希望你能制止她
for Delta Airlines, and I want you to stop her.
德尔塔可是大客户  我为什么要这么做
Delta would be a huge client; why would I want to stop her?
因为她这么做只是为了阻碍我
Because she only went after them to stop me
跟盖文·安德鲁签约  队友
from signing Gavin Andrews, and team mates
可不带这么坑队友的
don't do that to each other.
团队精神听上去是很棒棒
This team mate talk sounds great,
但你也才抢了她一个老客户
but you just went after one of her old clients.
我选择盖文不是因为他是她的老客户
I didn't choose Gavin because he was hers.
是因为盖文
I chose Gavin
是罗伯特·赞恩最金贵的客户
because he was the most valuable client to Robert Zane.
我只是没有被他是她的客户的事实吓住
The fact that he was hers just wasn't gonna stop me.
是吓住你  还是诱惑你
Wasn't gonna stop you, or was icing on the cake?
那又怎么样
What difference does that make?
考虑到你拜托我做的事
Well, considering what you're asking me to do,
这可有本质上的区别
it makes all the difference.
路易  在赞恩成为
Louis, after Zane ended up
执行合伙人之后我就想比下她
as managing partner I wanted to take her on,
但你说我应该先去和赞恩建立伙伴关系
but you said I should make a friend of Zane instead.
所以我想通过拿下盖文震撼罗伯特
So I went after Gavin to impress Robert,
如果你不想帮我阻止她
and if you're not gonna stop her,
我还不如一开始就和她宣战
I might as well just have gone after her in the first place.
行了行了  亚历克斯
All right, Alex, okay.
但你要说放弃那个八位数的摇钱树
But giving up a client with eight-figure billables
好比让我断条腿  所以我要帮了你
is going out on one hell of a limb, so I do this,
那你最好给我搞定盖文·安德鲁
you better deliver Gavin Andrews.
我会的  路易
I will, Louis.
我答应你
You have my word.
萨曼莎·惠勒
Samantha Wheeler.
我跟你谈一谈
You and I need to have a little chat.
路易·利特  瞧是什么风把您给吹来了
Louis Litt. To what do I owe the pleasure?
你懂我的
Oh, you know who I am.
您声名远扬
Well, a man like yourself needs no introduction.
小嘴真甜
That is very kind of you,
但我可不是来这儿听你拍马屁的
but I'm not here for you to blow smoke up my ass.
我想想  亚历克斯是意识到
Let me guess: Alex realized
他之于我不过是螳臂当车了吧
he wasn't gonna stop me on his own.
他是意识到你在给他下计
He realized that you were trying to undermine him,
所以我才会专程来这儿告诉你
which is why I'm here to tell you
别再打德尔塔的主意了
that you're gonna stop pursuing Delta.
难以置信
I don't believe this.
你真是站在这儿告诉我
Are you seriously coming in here to tell me
不准我跟世界上最大的航空公司签约吗
I can't sign one of the world's biggest airlines?
没错
Yeah, I am.
没得讨论  这是命令
And this isn't a discussion; it's an order.
我希望你还是
I hope you've had a chance
好好的
to think long
郑重考虑考虑
and hard about this.
换做是我  就不会这么鲁莽
Because I'd be careful what you wish for.
你这是在威胁我吗
You trying to intimidate me?
不过是一个小小的建议
Just giving you a little advice.
那你给我挺好了  小姑娘
Well, listen here, sweet face.
我懂的
I get it.
你现在风头正盛
You're the it girl.
你知道我是谁吗
Well, you know who I am?
我是利特家族的男人
I'm Litt man.
你再怎么在这儿搔首弄姿
And you can try to sashay your six-foot frame around here
好比1985年的布里吉特·尼尔森
like you're Brigitte Nielsen in 1985--
好莱坞女星
想把我整的晕头转向  缴械投降
turn me into a puddle, get me to capitulate.
那我可告诉你  没门儿
Well, I got news for you: it's not gonna happen.
行吧
All right.
德尔塔我不要了
I'll drop Delta.
我就知道你很通情达理的
I knew you'd see things my way.
但总有一天
But someday...
你会跪下来求我
you're gonna come asking for a favor.
也许不在不久的将来
Might not be today, might not be tomorrow,
但一定会有那么一天
but it's gonna happen...
那一天到来的时候
and when it does...
我还会记得今天
I'm gonna remember this conversation.
路易
And Louis?
如果你不觉得我能把你打得落花流水
If you think I couldn't turn you into a puddle,
你就大错特错了
you are wildly mistaken.
我们扯平了  你放弃那个客户
So we're clear. You'll drop the client.
我现在要出去一下
I have to go somewhere now.
你当然要去了
I'm sure you do.
布莱恩
Brian.
怎么了  你看起来很迷茫
What's going on? You look lost.
没有  只是要来不及了
I'm not lost. I'm just under the gun.
你知道卡特里娜在哪吗
Have you seen Katrina?
不知道  怎么了
No, why?
毕格罗就在会议室
Bigelow Textiles is in the conference room
会议五分钟前就该开始了
and the meeting was scheduled for five minutes ago.
-我不知道该怎么办  -别紧张
- I don't know what to do. - Easy.
卡特里娜从来不会缺席任何会议
Katrina's never missed a meeting in her life.
如果现在她不在  一会儿就去了
If she's not there, she will be.
你先去主持一下
Just go ahead and start.
问题是  我一小时前才拿到案子
Thing is, I just got the case an hour ago.
我已经尽力了
I'm hazy on the particulars at best.
我认为应该取消会面
I think I should cancel.
我觉得不太好
I don't think that's a good idea.
但如果我去主持会议
But what happens if I start the meeting
但她根本没来呢
and she doesn't show up at all?
如果你取消了会议
And what happens when you cancel the meeting
她一会儿又出现了呢
and she shows up three minutes later?
-唐娜  -布莱恩
- Donna. - Brian, look.
我知道你的能力  我相信
I know your value, and I believe
卡特里娜也知道  但事实上
that Katrina knows your value, but the truth is,
不久前  你还差点被裁员
not too long ago, you were on the chopping block.
这案子给了你
If you've been invited in on this case,
你就有机会证明自己
you're being offered another chance.
因为卡特里娜迟到而取消会议
And canceling a meeting that Katrina's running
不是我证明自己的方式
a little late to isn't the way to prove myself.
对  不是
No, it's not.
你说得对
You're right.
我这就去
I'll get it going.
哈维
Harvey.
你知道为什么
Is there a reason why
四十九楼的洗手间堵了吗
the 49th floor toilets have been backed up?
我怎么会知道
Why would I know that?
因为我找人维修
Because when I called to have it fixed,
他们说至少要四小时
they said they couldn't get to it for another four hours
与此同时  也许你能去看一下
and in the mean time, maybe you could take a look at it.
该死
Son of a bitch.
你  你  还有你
You, you, you.
放下手头的东西  跟我来会议室
Drop what you're doing and meet me in the conference room.
但我们在...
We're working on something...
我不管你在做什么
I don't give a shit what you're working on.
五分钟内来会议室
Conference room, five minutes.
哈维
Harvey.
唐娜  我正忙着呢
Donna, I'm in the middle of something.
我看出来了  你能告诉我
I can see that. Do you mind telling me
这和洗手间有什么关系
what that something has to do with those toilets?
这和大卫·福克斯有关  他想打一架
It has to do with the fact that David Fox wants a fight
我奉陪
and I'm gonna give him one.
为什么
A fight about what?
他不想给清洁女工付加班费
He doesn't want to pay our cleaning woman overtime.
等等  所以你把正在做
Hang on, so you're pulling the associates
韦斯特合并的同事拉过来帮她吗
off the Vistech merger to help her?
好吧  你想让我用其他同事吗
Fine, you want me to use different associates?
可以
I will.
我不在乎你用哪些同事
I don't care what associates you're using.
我想说大卫·福克斯可不好惹
I want to explain to you that David Fox is no joke.
据我了解  你不应该
And as noble as it sounds, you don't want
因为这种事和他对着干
to get in a fight with him over something like this.
我知道  唐娜  我和赞恩也这么说
I know that, Donna. That's what I said to Zane.
-但是...  -但是什么
- But... - But what?
哈维  这不是我们的行事风格
Harvey, this isn't what we do.
迈克就会这么做
Mike would have done it.
迈克已经不在这了
And Mike's not here anymore because he finally came
因为他最终想要做的和我们不同
to terms with the fact that this isn't what we do.
如果你告诉赞恩  你觉得不值得这么做
Look, if you told Zane you knew this wasn't worth it,
那你已经明白我说的没错
then you already know I'm right.
好吧  唐娜  你说得对
Okay, Donna. You're right.
让那些同事继续工作吧
Tell those associates to get back to whatever they were working on.
毕格罗先生  很高兴见到你
Mr. Bigelow, nice to meet you.
抱歉我们有些迟了
I'm sorry we're running a little late.
我是布莱恩·阿特曼
I'm Brian Altman.
卡特里娜到底在哪
Where the hell's Katrina?
她马上就来
I'm sure she'll be right here.
我现在能...
In the mean time, can I offer you--
不  我没有那么多时间
No, no, no. I don't have time for the meantime.
如果班尼特女士不能准时的话
If Ms. Bennett can't bother showing up on time,
她可以到时再寒暄
she can play catch-up when she gets here.
好的  我明白您时间有限
Okay, I see you're in a hurry.
我们从头梳理一下报告吧
Let's go through the report from the top.
我不需要你来读报告
I don't need you to read me the damn report.
我需要答案
What I need are some answers.
好的  你想知道什么
Um, all right. What do you want to know?
我们现在是什么情况
What kind of exposure are we looking at, here?
肯尼斯起诉你违背了合同
Well, Kineserve claims you improperly broke your contract,
但董事会议没有记录说明你不守信用
but the board minutes don't indicate any bad faith on your part.
-这是好消息  -坏消息呢
- That's the good news. - And the bad news?
会议记录也没给出
The minutes don't show any discussion of good cause
一个有力的理由让你终止合同
for terminating the contract, either.
没有有力的理由吗
No good cause?
你看过邮寄材料了吗
Did you see the delivery manifests?
我要再看一下
Um, I'd have to take another look at them before weighing in.
再看一下
Another look?
压力测试的结果怎么样
What about the stress test results?
对了
Right.
让我找一找
Let me just find that.
你没看全会议记录  对吧
You haven't even read all the goddamn minutes, have you?
我一定只漏了那部分
I must have just missed that part.
请让我找一下
If you'd just let me find it...
我觉得我们在浪费时间
I can see what's going on, here.
卡特里娜觉得我不值得她花时间
Katrina didn't think I was worthy of her attention,
所以她把我推给一个不合格的二流律师
so she pawned me off on some incompetent, second-rate associate.
毕格罗先生  我保证不是这样的
Mr. Bigelow, I can assure you that is not the case.
卡特里娜很重视与你的合作
Katrina values your business very much,
我也是个称职的律师
and I am a fully capable attorney.
我没看出来
Not from what I see.
如果不给我找个合格的律师
And if I can't be handled by a competent attorney,
那我就没必要和你们公司合作
I don't see why I should be handled by this firm at all.
请等一下  毕格罗先生
Please, Mr. Bigelow.
如果我们重新过一遍
Um, if we could just reset,
我们就可以重回正轨
I think we got off on the wrong foot.
你想重新来一遍吗
You wanna reset?
免了吧  我根本不应该坐在这
Get your shit together, 'cause I'm not about to sit here
看着你结结巴巴地表演
and watch you bumble your way through something
你完全没准备过的东西
you're clearly not prepared for.
下次会面如果
And the next time you call me in for a meeting
卡特里娜不在
without Katrina Bennett,
就不用叫我了
don't bother calling me in at all.
简直不敢相信
I don't believe this.
布莱恩
Brian...
你叫我自己去见客户  但你呢
No, you sent me in to a meeting by myself, and you're, what?
去公园散步了吗
Out taking a stroll around the park?
-等一下再谈  -就现在
- Please, not now. - Yes, now,
因为我刚刚被你的客户骂得狗血淋头
because I just got my ass handed to me by your client.
我没去散步
I wasn't taking a stroll.
我去了洗手间  因为那是整栋楼里
I was in the bathroom in a stall because it's the only place
唯一安静没有光线的地方
in this entire building that's dark and quiet.
-你在说什么  -我的偏头痛发作了
- What are you talking about? - I had a migraine.
最严重的一次
One of the worst I've ever had.
要开会的时候
And when it was time for the meeting
我打开门  但即使戴着太阳镜
I opened the door, but even with the sunglasses
光线都让我感觉脑袋中插满冰锥
the light made it feel like there were icicles
所以我无法离开
in my head, and I couldn't leave.
布莱恩  对不起
Brian, I'm so sorry.
我不知道你有偏头痛
I had no idea you get migraines.
我高中后就没得过了
I haven't had one since high school.
-压力又让病情复发  -你是说
- They're triggered by stress. - You mean like the stress
像必须裁掉一堆新律师的压力
of having to fire a bunch of associates.
我第二天就犯病了
They started the day after.
-你得告诉路易  -不
- You need to tell Louis. - No.
绝不能让路易知道
Louis is the last person who can know about this.
你为什么要瞒着他
Why would you want to hide this from him?
因为不是每天都有当高级合伙人的机会
Because you don't get nine shots at senior partner;
机会就一个
you get one.
你要成为高级合伙人了
You're up for senior partner.
是的
I am.
这事不该让人知道  甚至包括我
No one is supposed to know about this, not even me.
如果我突然患上偏头痛
And if suddenly I start getting migraines
让人看起来我无法胜任这项工作...
that make it seem like I can't handle the job...
我不会告诉任何人
No one's gonna find out anything from me.
-但毕格罗真的很生气  -毕格罗
- But Bigelow is pretty pissed. - Well, Bigelow isn't going
明天不会撤案动议
to be at the motion to dismiss tomorrow,
所以只要我赢下案子  我们就没事
so as long as I win that, we'll be fine.
那我最好去勇敢面对路易
In the meantime, I'd better go face the music with Louis.
布莱恩  你不必这么做
Brian, you don't have to do that.
如果我不去  他就会发现
If I don't, he's gonna find out
你得偏头痛的事
about your migraines.
直接点
Be direct.
告诉他你很抱歉
Tell him you're sorry.
他可能不会高兴  但他会尊重你的
He might not be happy, but he'll respect you.
布莱恩
Brian.
如果曾经有对于你
If ever there were any doubt
是否是有价值新律师的怀疑
about you being a valuable associate...
今后都不会再有了
there isn't anymore.
安娜  我是哈维·斯佩克特
Anna, it's Harvey Specter.
斯佩克特先生
Mr. Specter.
我没想到你这么快就有了回复
I didn't expect to hear from you so soon.
-这就是说... -恐怕
- Does this mean that-- - I'm afraid
-这事行不通  -什么
- it's not gonna work. - What?
我跟他们谈过  但我无能为力
I tried talking to them, and there's nothing I can do.
你是说你不想给自己的公司
You mean you don't want to make a problem
-带来麻烦  -不
- for your firm. - No.
安娜
Anna...
我可以向你推荐另一间律所
there's another firm out there I can recommend to you.
我没钱找其它律所
I can't afford to pay another firm.
你不必付钱
You wouldn't have to.
过去办这种案子的那个人
Look, the guy who used to do cases like this
已经不在这里  但他去了一个法律诊所
doesn't work here anymore, but he used to work at a clinic,
我是说把你的事交给那边
and I'm talking about setting you up there.
我早该知道
I should have known
-你会把我推出去  -我不是推你出去
- you'd pawn me off. - I'm not pawning you off.
我保证  我会去法律诊所
I promise, I will go down there and make sure
保证我认识的两个律师亲自处理此事
one of the two lawyers I know handles this personally.
好吧
Okay.
如果你相信这个诊所  那我就相信你
If you trust this firm, then I trust you.
我们保持联系
I'll be in touch.
绝对没错
Yes, absolutely.
我完全同意
I agree 100%.
不会再发生了
Never again.
路易  我能跟你谈谈吗
Hey, Louis, can I talk to you for a second?
当然  因为我想知道
Sure as hell can, 'cause I wanna know
会议上到底发生了什么
what the ---- happened in that meeting.
-我就是为此过来... -算了
- That's what I came-- - You know what, never mind.
我没必要听了
I don't need to hear it,
因为我刚挂掉约翰·毕格罗的电话
because I just got off the phone with John Bigelow,
他告诉我你回答不了一个简单问题
and he tells me that you couldn't answer a goddamn question.
我知道  我只是...
I know that, and I just--
我引用他的原话说
He also says, and I quote,
"我再也不想跟布莱恩·阿特曼见面"
"I never want to be in another meeting with Brian Altman again."
对不起  路易  对不起
I--I'm sorry, Louis. I'm sorry.
你抱歉
You're sorry?
你要说的就只有道歉吗
That's all you have to say for yourself?
因为你刚让卡特里娜失望了
Because you just let down Katrina.
你明白我在说什么吗
Do you understand what I'm saying to you?
-我明白  -我认为你不明白
- I do. - I do not think that you do.
因为她想炒了你  布莱恩  而我阻止了
Because she wanted to fire you, Brian, and I wouldn't let her.
然后她给了你第二次机会
Then she gives you a second chance,
你就这么表现吗
and you do this?
你还有什么借口  布莱恩
What the hell is your excuse, Brian?
你是工作失职  还是你想故意
Do you just suck at your job, or are you actively trying
破坏直接上司的权威
to undermine a direct supervisor?
-我想是我工作失职  -这种事
- I guess I suck at my job. - Something like this
再也不会发生  别说被炒了
ever happens again, forget about being fired.
你会希望自己从未出生
You're gonna wish you were never born.
快滚  因为现在不止是约翰·毕格罗
Now get out, because right now John Bigelow isn't the only one
再也不想看见你
who never wants to see your face again.
你好  有什么要帮忙的吗
Hi, can I help you?
纳森·克鲁格在吗
Is Nathan Krueger here?
纳森去费城办案了
Nathan's in Philadelphia on a case.
奥利佛·格雷迪呢
How about Oliver Grady?
奥利佛和一位客户出去了
Oliver's out with a client.
有什么我能帮你的吗
Is there something I can help you with?
不用了  谢谢
No, thanks.
我要告诉他们有人来过吗
Can I tell them who stopped by?
没关系  我已经耽误你够久了
It's okay; I've taken enough of your time.
-这是我想的那个东西吗  -雷诺阿
- Is that what I think it is? - Renoir.
已签字  已盖章  已递交
Signed, sealed, and delivered.
介意告诉我你怎么拿到的吗
Mind telling me how you pulled it off?
当然  在你交给我签署委托书的时候
Absolutely, as soon as you hand me a signed engagement letter.
你知道吗  我还有个更好的消息
You know what, I'm gonna do you one better.
不如你拿出手机
Why don't you take out your phone and check out
看看报刊的最新版
the latest edition of the "Journal."
不敢相信
I don't believe it.
你发布声明说我们是你的新律师
You issued an announcement saying we're your new attorneys.
我说过你是我的人  我不介意公诸于世
I told you, you're my guy, and I don't mind the world knowing it.
-那么你想挂在哪里  -无所谓
- So where do you want this? - I don't give a shit,
因为不会在这里挂太久
'cause it's not gonna be here long.
什么
What?
我要把它运到开曼群岛
I'm shipping it to the Cayman Islands
一家航空公司会出价5500万买画
where a certain airline company's gonna pay me $55 million for it.
我以为你说它只值16万
I thought you said it was only worth 16,
而你永远不会卖掉它
and that you'd never sell it.
这就是艺术的真谛
Well, that's the thing about art:
艺术品的价值依观看者而定
the value is in the eye of the beholder.
我想让你看看这个
I want you to behold this.
你想让我通过开曼群岛的保密信托
You want me on-shore 55 million
让5500万入境
from a blind trust in the Caymans?
盖文  我得告诉你  这看起来
Gavin, I have to tell you, this looks a hell of lot
-非常像是洗钱  -那么好在
- like laundering money. - Well, then it's a good thing
你不确定是不是洗钱  因为你不知情
you don't know that for sure, because if you don't know it
你就能做  而你得这么做
you can do it, and you're going to do it.
我懂了
I get it.
你向我编了个故事
You gave me a bullshit story about this thing
说这画有情感价值来引我入套
having sentimental value to rope me in.
然后你发布声明称
then you put out an announcement saying
我们是你的律师
we're your attorneys.
而现在  如果我不这么做
And now, if I don't do this,
你甩掉我们  外界就以为
you drop us and the world thinks
我们在一天内就搞砸了
we shit the bed inside of a day.
你脑子转得挺快
You catch on quick.
-我不会这么做  -或许你会
- I'm not doing it. - Maybe you will,
或许不会
maybe you won't.
但你最好想想怎么和罗伯特·赞恩解释
But you'd better think about how you're gonna explain to Robert Zane
你如何在两天内签下我又失去我的
how you signed me and lost me inside of two days.
你在这儿啊  我一直在等你
There you are. I've been waiting for you
给我找点活儿干
to give me something to do.
没剩多少了  所以我自己处理就好
There isn't much left to do, so I'm handling it myself.
卡特里娜  别这样  还剩好多事要做呢
Katrina, come on, there's a ton of work left.
我看得出你还在难过
I can see you're still in pain.
肯定有什么事是我能做的
There must be something I can do.
我会没事的
I'll be fine.
要是我把所有灯都打开呢
What if I turned all the lights on?
那样你会好过点吗
Would you be fine then?
卡特里娜  因为明天法庭上
Katrina, 'cause that's what it's gonna be like
-就是灯光大亮的  -布莱恩
- in court tomorrow. - Brian.
我听说路易的事了
I heard what happened with Louis,
我不会让历史重演的
and I'm not going to let that happen again.
听我说
Listen to me.
我说会帮你保守秘密的时候
I knew what I signed up for
我知道自己卷进了什么事
when I said I'd keep your situation a secret.
对此我很感激
And I appreciate it.
明天我会走上法庭
And now I'm going to go into court tomorrow
尽我所能
and do the best I can.
卡特里娜  你给了我第二次机会
Katrina, you gave me a second chance,
而当时  你承认了自己的错误
and when you did, you admitted you were wrong.
不是谁都做得到这一点
Not everyone would do that.
而这样的人正是我所希望的高级合伙人
And someone that would is exactly the kind of person
我想要让这样的人领导
I want to have leading me as a senior partner.
所以要是你不愿让我替你做
So if you won't let me do this for you,
至少让我们一起面对吧
at least let's do it together.
好吧  布莱恩  我们一起
Okay, Brian. We'll do it together.
亚历克斯  不管你有什么事
Alex, whatever it is,
我都要和客户共进晚餐
I'm meeting a client for dinner.
没问题  我只有一个问题
That's okay, I just have one question.
-你知不知道  -知道什么
- Did you know? - Know what?
盖文·安德鲁本来要找我给他洗钱
That Gavin Andrews was gonna ask me to launder money for him.
真不敢相信  你一直都知道
I don't believe it. You knew it the whole time.
我不知道
No, I didn't.
但我知道他有事找你做
But I knew he was gonna ask you to do something.
那你跟我就得上楼去
Then you and I are gonna go upstairs
立马想出脱身的办法
and figure out how to get out of this, right now.
你是不是疯了
Are you out of your mind?
我才不会靠近那人的会计所在的地方
I'm not going anywhere near that man's account.
你必须去  因为你知道我的过去
Yes, you are, because you knew my history
却还是让我签了他
and you let me sign him anyway.
你他妈是在开玩笑吗
Are you ----ing kidding me?
你可是我一手带起来的
I brought up your history.
那你也知道我不能信任你
And you knew I was in no position to trust you.
对此我又能怎么办呢
And what I was I supposed to do about that?
你总可以告诉我一点详情吧
You could have given me some goddamn specifics.
因为你总能拿出点什么
'Cause there's no way you didn't have something
让我相信你说的是实话
that would have convinced me you were telling the truth.
那我又怎么能相信你不会
And how was I supposed to trust you wouldn't use
-用我说的话来对付我  -我不会这样做
- whatever I said against me? - I wouldn't do that.
那要是我说
Oh? So if I had said,
亚历克斯  别签那个人
"Hey, Alex, don't sign this guy.
他要让你掩盖一桩凶杀案
He's gonna ask you to cover up a murder."
你敢说不会用这句话对付我
You weren't gonna use that?
他让你做这种事吗
Is that what he asked you to do?
我跟你没得聊了
This conversation is over.
你是自食其果  别因为苦果难吃
You made your bed. Don't come crying to me
-就来找我哭鼻子  -我不会找人哭鼻子
- because the sheets are dirty. - I'm not gonna cry to anyone.
这个人的情况我会对赞恩实话实说
I'm gonna tell Zane exactly what this man is all about,
等他发现你做的破事
and we'll see what happens
我们再来看事情会怎么发展
when he finds out whatever shit you did.
你以为罗伯特不知道吗
You don't think Robert knew?
你以为我们离开兰考律所时
Why do you think he didn't fight
他没有争取盖文的生意是为了什么
for Gavin's business when we left Rand Kaldor?
你是说赞恩知道你做违法的事
You're saying Zane knows you did illegal shit?
我是说罗伯特·赞恩知道盖文·安德鲁
I'm saying, Robert Zane knew what kind of a client
是个什么样的客户  而我知道怎么对付
Gavin Andrews was, that I knew how to handle him,
但我不想再应对他了
and that I stopped wanting to.
那就帮我脱身
Then help me get out of this.
-我为什么呢  -因为我们在同一战线
- Why should I? - Because we're on the same team,
这总该有点意义吧
and that's supposed to mean something,
尤其是涉及到违法事宜的时候
especially when it's about breaking the law.
求你了萨曼莎
Please, Samantha.
我本该听你的话  但我还有家人
I should have listened to you, but I have a family.
我不能让他们受伤害  我承受不起
I can't afford to do something that'll hurt them.
好吧  亚历克斯
Okay, Alex.
你是有家的人
You are a family man.
-而他不是  -你什么意思
- He is not. - What are you saying?
我是说  你是那种不惜采取
I'm saying, you're the kind of man
任何手段都要保护家庭的人
that would go to any length to protect your family.
盖文·安德鲁则是那种
Gavin Andrews is the kind of man
不惜一切代价保护自己的人
that would go to any length to protect himself.
所以我们只需以实质性违约开始
So all we need to do is open with material breach,
表明中止条款不适用
show severability doesn't apply,
再以无法履行结尾就好
then close with impossibility of performance.
我们这么一来
We do all that,
就给了他们的说法致命一击
it'll drive the stake right through their claim.
我们
We?
是的  我们
Yes, we.
因为虽然我感觉好些了
Because although I'm feeling better,
但你付出的和我一样多
you did this as much as I did,
所以我们应该一起出庭
which means we should do it together.
-你确定吗  -我确定
- You sure? - I'm sure.
我敢肯定
I do believe that's the first time
自打这事开始  这是我第一次见你笑
I've seen you smile since we started this whole thing.
我只是想起了高三的时候
I was just thinking about my senior year of high school.
我就是这样做作业的
This is how I used to do my homework.
你高中时会找人帮你一起写论文吗
You had an associate write your papers for you in high school?
有个人陪我一起学习
I had a study partner.
他是我最好的朋友
He was my best friend.
我们从前会一起写论文  写得飞快
We used to write our papers together by flash light.
从没想过这么多年后我还能做同样的事
Never thought I'd be doing the same thing years later.
你跟他还有联系吗
You in touch with him?
没了
No.
但今晚之后感觉又有了
But I feel like I am after tonight.
一看你笑我就知道说的话有多土了
Now you're smiling. I know it sounds cheesy.
不  我只是想到了一周前的事
No, I was just thinking about where we were a week ago
那时我以为你是冷面无情的人
when I thought you were cold and heartless.
这么快就从冷面无情变成了
And I went from that to being your best friend
-最好的朋友  -这么说也不太对
- in record time. - I wouldn't say best friends.
只有我们成了最好的朋友时
Well, you can only say stuff like that to me
你才能跟我说这种话
because we're, like, best friends.
这我可不知道
Well, I don't know about that.
但我们也算够亲近  我要告诉你
But we are close enough for me to tell you
明天你要一个人出庭了
that you're going to go to court by yourself tomorrow.
你不是说你感觉好多了吗
But I thought you said you were feeling better.
确实  但你做了这么多来证明
I am, but you did all this to help prove
我当得起管理的职位
that I could manage people,
要是我不给你个机会向约翰·毕格罗
and what kind of manager would I be
证明自己  我得是多糟糕的管理者
if I didn't give you a chance to prove yourself to John Bigelow?
-你确定吗  -我确定
- You sure? - I'm sure.
你说你得去趟中央公园是什么意思
What do you mean you gotta go down to Central?
要花多久
How long's that gonna take?
该花多久就花多久
It's gonna take as long as it takes.
-这里出什么事了  -罗伯特  你还好吗
- What the hell is going on, here? - Robert, you all right?
-你看起来糟透了  -电梯不停我这层
- You look like hell. - The elevator wouldn't stop on our floor.
我只能在45层下电梯  一路爬上来
Had to get off at 45 and hike the rest of the way up here.
天啊  你可得锻炼身体了
God damn, man, you gotta keep in shape.
-只不过五层楼而已  -我们非得
- That was only five floors. - Is that really the problem
谈论这个问题吗  路易
we need to talk about, Louis?
不  其实一小时前
No. In fact, an hour ago,
-电梯就彻底罢工了  -该死
- the elevators weren't working at all. - Shit.
而现在这个小混蛋说
And now this ass clown says
他需要房东的许可才能买一根保险丝
that he needs to have landlord's approval to order a simple fuse.
-什么  -我说他...
- What? - I said that he's--
我知道你说了什么  我要听他亲口说
I know what you said. I wanna hear it from him.
你想让我说什么
What do you want me to say?
我从我的上级那得到的指示
I got orders from my supervisor.
没有福克斯先生同意不能订购新的零件
No new parts without Mr. Fox's specific approval.
路易  我看明白了
Louis, I know what's going on here.
-你指什么  -我指发生的这一切
- What are you talking about? - I'm talking about the fact
根本不是什么鬼巧合
that this is no goddamn coincidence.
安娜  我是哈维·斯佩克特
Anna, it's Harvey Specter.
好消息  我决定亲自接管你的案子了
I've got good news: I've decided to take care of you myself.
我今天早上去上班的时候
Because I showed up to work this morning
他们告诉我我被炒了
and they told me I was fired,
而且我不应该浪费时间去寻求什么
and that I shouldn't bother applying to any...
安娜  我现在有点脱不开身的事要办
Anna, I got something I can't reschedule right this second.
-我得  -求你了  斯佩克特先生
- I'm gonna have to-- - Please, Mr. Specter.
之前我可能状态很糟糕
I was in horrible shape before,
但现在我真的走投无路了
but now I don't know what to do.
听着  我会告诉你该怎么做的
Look, I'll tell you what we're gonna do
五分钟后我就给你打回去
I'm gonna call you back in five minutes,
你得把发生的事一字不差地告诉我
you're gonna tell me exactly what happened.
我不会就这么放过他们的
because I'm not gonna let them get away with this.
好了  哈维  那个保洁的
Okay, Harvey, what the hell is going on
-是怎么他妈回事  -罗伯特
- with that cleaning woman? - Robert...
你说你不想挑起争斗  但你还是做了
You said you weren't going to pick a fight, and you did.
而现在我们的电梯全都故障了
And now our elevators aren't working.
你想知道发生了什么吗
You wanna know what's going on?
大卫·福克斯为了报复安娜把她开除了
David Fox just retaliated against Anna by firing her,
而我马上将要打的他满地找牙
and I'm about to knock his teeth out.
-你不能这么干  -淡定点  罗伯特
- You will do no such thing. - Relax, Robert.
我们能应付来一两个堵了的马桶的
We can handle a clogged toilet or two.
你听见我刚刚说的什么了吗
Did you hear what I just said?
我不是在说马桶
I'm not talking about toilets.
那个男人刚刚停用了我们的电梯
The man just shut down our elevators,
而我是不会同意仅仅因为你觉得
and I'm not gonna let us start losing clients
清洁工人比公司的需要还重要
because you decided the cleaning staff is more important
就让我们产生客户流失的
than the needs of this firm.
我没做任何你没批准的事
I didn't do anything that you didn't sign off on.
放屁  你说你只会
Bullshit. You said that you were gonna
和那个人谈谈
have a two-minute conversation with the man,
如果你就干了这些
and if that's all you did
那他现在不可能蓄意给我们的工作添乱
he wouldn't be sabotaging our offices.
你知道吗  罗伯特
Well, you know what, Robert?
我不在乎他在对我们做什么
I don't care what he's doing to us.
我在乎的是他对她做了什么
I care what he's doing to her.
-你刚刚说什么  -我说我不在乎
- What did you just say? - I said I don't care
-他在对我们做什么  -我在乎
- what he's doing to us. - Well, I do.
-什么  -你听见了  哈维
- Excuse me? - You heard me, Harvey.
我不管你觉得自己在干什么
I don't know what it is you think you're doing,
-但你需要停手了  -难以置信
- but it needs to stop. - I don't believe this.
-你居然站在他那边了  -对  哈维
- You're siding with him. - Yes, Harvey, I am.
你可能不想听到这个  哈维
And you're not gonna want to hear this either, Harvey,
但我也是
but I am too.
因为如果你继续让事端扩大
Because if you keep escalating this,
就不仅仅是几部故障电梯的问题了
it's not just gonna be about broken elevators.
他会找到方法把我们踢出这栋楼的
He's gonna find a way to kick us out of the building.
好啊  那你们可能也都不想听到这个
Well, none of you are gonna want to hear this,
但我他妈才不在乎
but I don't give a shit
他会不会把我们踢出这栋楼
whether he kicks us out of the building or not.
够了
That's enough.
你不能因为这种小事
You don't go to war with the guy
就和这栋楼的所有人开战
that owns your house over something like this.
把它了解掉  就今天
End it, and end it today.
我能和你一起吗
May I join you?
你一般不问我这种问题
You don't usually ask that.
可从我们在检察院起
And you haven't made your own copies
你就没亲自复印过东西了
since we were at the DA's office.
大概是吧
I guess I haven't.
哈维  我以为你会把这个案子
Harvey, I thought that you were gonna
送到法律诊所去
take this thing to the clinic.
我去了  唐娜
That's what I did, Donna.
但纳森和奥利佛不在
But Nathan and Oliver weren't there;
而每个桌子上的案子都堆的比山高
there were cases piled high on every desk;
没有人会像我一样
and nobody there would care about her
这么在乎她  所以
the way I needed them to, so...
我就转身出来了
I turned around and I walked right out.
-我明白了  -我怎么变成这样的  唐娜
- I see. - How did I get here, Donna?
跟路易和罗伯特站在对立面上  还有你
I'm at odds with Robert and Louis, and now even you,
就因为两个月前的一件我根本
over something two months ago shouldn't have even shown up
不会在乎的小事
on my radar.
我来告诉你你是怎么搞得吧
I'll tell you how you got here...
真不敢相信你开始进入这个状态时
and I can't believe I didn't see this
我居然没看出来
the second you started this thing.
哈维  你想迈克了
Harvey, you're missing Mike.
-你什么意思  -你看不出来吗
- What are you talking about? - Don't you see?
这个案子里到处都是迈克·罗斯的影子
This case has Mike Ross written all over it.
你从法律诊所走出来
And you didn't walk out of that clinic
不是因为纳森和奥利佛不在
because Nathan and Oliver weren't there;
而是因为迈克不在
you walked out because Mike wasn't there.
那我能怎么做呢  唐娜
Well, what am I supposed to do about that, Donna?
这个女人需要帮助
Because this woman needs help,
我不可能就让她这么自生自灭
and I am not gonna throw her out on the street.
如果是我  我会打给迈克
Tell you what I'd do. I'd call Mike.
如果有人也曾陷入过这样的困境
If there's anyone who's been in a situation
那就是他
like this before, it's him,
而他最擅长逃出困境
and he's the best person to figure a way out.
但是哈维  你需要尽快这么做
But Harvey, you've got to do it soon,
因为罗伯特和路易是对的
because Robert and Louis are right.
你需要放手
You have to let this thing go.
-事情结了吗  -结了
- Is it done? - It is done.
很好
Good.
-没那么难吧  -对我来说不难
- Wasn't so hard, was it? - Not for me.
这是什么
What's this?
你用我的钱干了什么
The hell did you do with my money?
我给你找到了一个不错的商业机会
I found you a legitimate business opportunity.
在他妈开曼群岛上
In the goddamn Cayman Islands?
大部分人都想回国投资
Funny thing: most people want to repatriate their money,
所以你如果搞搞本地投资的话
which means you can make a pretty sweet deal
可以大捞一笔
by investing locally instead.
你不能这么做  你没这个权利
You can't do this. You don't have the authority.
我现在有了  因为站在你对面的人
I do now, because you're looking
是你新的财产受托人
at the new trustee of your account.
-那不可能  -是吗
- That's impossible. - Is it?
你让你的侄女当受托人来为你背锅
Pretty smart making your niece trustee
很精明嘛
to insulate yourself.
当然啦  当我告诉她你就是设计让她
Of course, when I told her you set her up to take the fall
在出事时替你担责任的时候
if authorities ever found out where your money came from,
她很高兴地就把控制权转让给我了
she was more than happy to sign over control to me.
我不相信
I don't believe you.
那你给她打给电话吧
Pick up the phone and call her.
不过她很生你的气倒是
She's kind of pissed at you, though.
今年感恩节可能会有点尴尬
Thanksgiving might be weird this year.
你个婊子养的  你出卖了我
You son of a bitch. You sold me out.
不  盖文  我没有
No, Gavin, I didn't.
我做的事都是在为你的最优利益考虑
I did what's in your best interest,
虽然你傻到看不明白
regardless of the fact that you're too stupid to see it.
-你被炒了  -我不这么觉得
- You're fired. - I don't think so.
因为如果我能这么对你
Because if I can do this to you,
想象一下我为了你能做什么吧
imagine what I can do for you.
但如果你再让我做类似这种事
But if you ever ask me to do anything like this ever again,
我不仅会举报你
I won't just turn you in.
我会把这笔基金都转让给你的侄女
I'll sign over every nickel of this trust to your niece,
和其他被你坑害过的亲戚
and every other relative you've ever screwed over.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
明白了
We're clear.
路易  我能和你谈谈吗
Louis, can I talk to you for a minute?
当然  但首先
Of course. But first,
看来要恭喜了
I understand congratulations are in order.
听说你今天在庭上赢了一局
I heard you won in court today.
这就是我要说的
That's the thing.
赢的人不是我  是布莱恩
It wasn't me who won, Louis; it was Brian.
-什么  -听我解释
- What? - Just let me explain.
解释什么
Explain what?
解释委托人说了不要他你还让他上吗
That the client said "No Brian" and you didn't listen?
我不管委托人说了什么
I don't care what the client said
因为两年前  有位委托人说
because two years ago, another client said,
不要卡特里娜和瑞秋
"No Katrina" And "No Rachel,"
而你跟他们说见鬼去吧
and you told them to go to hell.
我为什么要
So why should I be any different
-不遵循你的教导  -因为  卡特里娜
as a manager than you? - Because, Katrina,
情况不一样
the situation was different.
你当时没有搞砸事情  布莱恩搞砸了
You didn't shit the bed; Brian did.
不  路易  他没有
No, Louis, he didn't.
是我
I did.
字幕
- What are you talking about?
我最近一直偏头痛  路易
I've been getting migraines, Louis.
小时候我曾经有段时间得过
I used to get them as a kid,
自从我开除了那些新律师
and ever since I had to fire those associates,
偏头痛就又犯了
I started getting them again.
而因为高级合伙人的事  你不敢告诉我
And you were afraid to tell me because of senior partner.
是的  我应该和布莱恩一起参会
Yes, and I was supposed to be in that meeting with Brian,
而他没有告诉你
and he didn't tell you about it
是为了保护我
because he was protecting me.
所以不是布莱恩的错  是我的
So it wasn't Brian's fault; it was yours.
没错
It was.
我知道你要把一切都告诉罗伯特
And I know you're gonna have to tell Robert everything,
我也知道这恐怕意味着我无法升职
and I know that probably means I won't be senior partner,
但我不能让布莱恩为了我毁掉前程
but I can't let Brian hurt his career for me.
卡特里娜  我唯一要告诉罗伯特的
Katrina, the only thing I'm gonna be telling Robert
就是你会是个很棒的高级合伙人
is that you're gonna make one hell of a senior partner.
那是我认为它是的东西吗
Is that what I think it is?
如果那是解决福克斯的计划  没错
If you think it's the plan to put this Fox thing to bed, then yes.
不错啊
This is good.
-迈克确实很聪明  -确实不错
- Mike's a pretty smart guy. - It is good,
但不是迈克想的  是我
but Mike didn't come up with it.I did.
既然如此我就直说了  确实还有瑕疵
Well, now that you mention it, I do see a bunch of flaws.
说真的  哈维  真的不错  但是
Seriously, Harvey, this is great, but...
你为什么没找迈克
why didn't you talk to Mike?
因为我觉得与其找他帮忙
Because I thought instead of calling and asking for a solution,
我更想找他说这个圆满结局的故事
I'd rather call and tell him a story with a happy ending.
而且也不能让小狗给大狗收拾麻烦
And you don't send in the puppy to clean up the dog's mess.
-差不多吧  -这样的话
- Something like that. - In that case,
-这个还给你  -不用
- you're gonna need this back. - No, I'm not,
因为这个要你交给大卫·福克斯
because you're gonna be the one to give it to David Fox.
-为什么  -因为我们还需要他同意
- Why me? - Because we still need to get him to agree,
而我们可以选择用礼还是用兵
and we can either do it with a sledgehammer or a velvet glove.
我懂了
I get it.
你是说我是兵
You're saying I'm a sledgehammer.
差不多吧
Something like that.
哈维  如果你要派我去
Listen, Harvey, if you're gonna send me in there
商量此事  我需要知道
to negotiate this, I need to know
我能全权决定如何商定此事
that I have carte blanche to do what it takes to close him.
我知道
I know.
字幕
You do.
你怎么想到的
How'd you think of this?
简单
Easy.
我就想  换了迈克他会怎么做
I just thought, "What would Mike do?"
唐娜·鲍尔森
Donna Paulsen.
-大卫·福克斯  -如果你来
- David Fox. - You know, if you're here
是为了拿清洁工的事骚扰我
to harass me about this cleaning lady,
那就请回吧
then you can just turn right around.
我来是为了这个
I'm here because of this.
你们要提起群体诉讼
You're filing a class-action lawsuit?
不是我们  是上东区法律诊所
We're not; East Side Legal Clinic is.
也就是说不管你要把我们怎么样
Which means that no matter what you do to us,
这诉讼案都不会受影响
it's not going away.
如果你再开除其他人
And if you try to fire anybody else,
你就会再接到一份诉讼
you'll be getting another one of those.
而且不会是因为加班  是因为报复
And it won't be for overtime; it'll be for retaliation.
你这辈子都要在法庭上度过的
You'll be in court for the rest of your life.
为什么来的是你不是哈维·斯佩克特
Why are you here instead of Harvey Specter?
因为如果哈维来  他扔了诉讼就会走人
Because if Harvey were here, he'd drop that down walk out,
然后跟你开战
and go to war with you.
而我呢  是来商量的
I, on the other hand, have a compromise.
-商量什么  -重新启用安娜·里德
- Which is? - Give Anna Reed her job back,
付他们应得的工资
you start paying those people what they're worth...
-然后呢  -然后你将得到为期一年的
- And? - You get free legal services
哈维·斯佩克特的免费法律咨询服务
from Harvey Specter himself for the next year.
得了  胡扯
Oh, come on. Bullshit.
他绝不会同意
There's no way he agrees to that.
他一定同意
Oh, he'll agree to it, all right.
你是说他都不知道
So you mean he doesn't already know about it.
还不知道
No, he doesn't.
但他授权给我商定此事
But he gave me the authority to close this thing,
而我认为这是唯一的方法
and that's what I've determined it's gonna take
因为如果不让对方难受一下
because neither one of you is gonna compromise
你们俩谁都不会放手
unless you know the other one is getting shafted.
-有个条件  -不行
- One condition. - Nope.
没有商量余地
This is take it or leave it.
-你都没听我的条件  -不行  我不愿意
- You won't even hear my condition. - No, I won't,
因为我毫无通过和你吃晚餐
because I have no interest in going to dinner with you
商定此事的意愿
to close this deal.
所以呢
So what's it gonna be?
开战  还是双赢
War or win-win?
早上把文件起草好  就成交
You set up the paperwork in the morning, we got a deal.
我给你个更好的方法
I'll do you one better.
你早上给我送来一份
Send it down in the morning.
我才不把时间浪费在这种事上
I got better things to do with my time.
这是什么
What's this?
巴克利终极格斗冠军赛近区门票
Floor-level tickets for the UFC at Barclays.
-调查很仔细啊  -是的
- You did your homework. - I did.
就像你事先提醒我
Like you told me I should have done
我该对盖文·安德鲁做的一样
with Gavin Andrews in the first place.
我想这就是说你搞定他了
I assume that means you took care of him?
他和他的破事都搞定了
And the horse he rode in on.
总之  我知道这件事结束前
Anyway, I know we'll probably end up
我们恐怕还要有
going toe-to-toe plenty of more times
很多摩擦冲突  但现在  晚安
before it's all over, but for now, good night.
你很有深度
You're more than meets the eye.
亚历克斯
Alex.
我知道你认为我们是在竞争同一件事
I know you think we're in competition for the same thing,
但不是的
but we're not.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
罗伯特·赞恩对我做出了承诺
Robert Zane made me a promise.
下一个上墙的名字一定是我的
The next name that goes up on the wall is mine.
为什么要告诉我
Why are you telling me this?
因为如果你总觉得我是为了超过你
Because we're never going to trust each other
我们是无法信任对方的
if you think I'm trying to get ahead of you.
我没有
I'm not.
因为我已经在你前面了
Because I already am.
晚安  萨曼莎
Good night, Samantha.
晚安  亚历克斯
Good night. Alex.